Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Newspaper Guild of New York Records
1935-1998
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Newspaper Guild of New York
WAG.125
552 Linear Feet in 552 record cartons
The Newspaper Guild of New York (The Newspaper Guild, Local 3) represents journalists, sales staff and technical workers in the print/online media in the New York metropolitan area. Among its members are reporters, photographers, editors, typographers, commercial artists, technicians, accountants, mail-room and circulation staff, independent translators, and staff members of non-profit organizations. The Guild has been active in campaigns to defeat racial and sex discrimination, to promote worker safety, and to provide job security in an industry that experienced rapid automation and other technical/structural changes. The Collection includes administrative and general files of the NGNY (including material on its parent union, The Newspaper Guild), and extensive files on individual "shops" or branches (generally associated with a specific employer or publication). Shop files document bargaining, contracts, grievances and arbitrations, social and political activities of shops, elections, the work of officers and staff, and changing technology, working conditions and industry trends.
Conditions Governing Access
The processed portion of the collection is open for research without restrictions; donor permission is required for boxes 235-551.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Newspaper Guild of New York (The Newspaper Guild, Local 3) represents journalists, sales staff, and technical workers in the print and online media industry in the New York metropolitan area. Among its members are reporters, photographers, editors, typographers, commercial artists, technicians, accountants, mail-room and circulation staff, independent translators, and staff members of non-profit organizations. The Guild has been active in campaigns to defeat racial and sex discrimination, to promote worker safety, and to provide job security in an industry that experienced rapid automation and other technical and structural changes.
The Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) was chartered in 1933 by a group of journalists led by Heywood Broun, columnist at the New York World Telegram. In December of the same year, representatives of disparate groups of journalists from across the country met in Washington, D.C. and formed the American Newspaper Guild (ANG). The driving forces behind creation of the Guild were Broun and Jonathan Eddy of the New York Times, both from the NYNG. There was considerable opposition within the fledgling Guild to operating as a trade union rather than as a professional association. In that internal struggle, the NYNG strongly supported the trade-union model. The bitter Newark Ledger strike of 1934-1935 proved to be a testing ground for conflicting visions of the Guild's role. While the strike settlement yielded little in the way of concrete gains for the strikers, the Guild emerged from it with an enhanced sense of national solidarity and confirmation of its ability to lead and bargain for its members.
At its founding, the American Newspaper Guild was open only to journalists, broadly defined. However, in 1937 it expanded its jurisdiction to include commercial departments, and added the goals of improved journalistic and ethical standards, and equal employment and advancement opportunities in the newspaper industry to its mission statement. The Guild affiliated with the American Federation of Labor in 1936, but soon abandoned the AFL for the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO).
The ensuing years saw increased international expansion as the Canadian region was established in the 1950s. In 1970, the ANG changed its name to The Newspaper Guild (TNG). Against the backdrop of the burgeoning Civil Rights Movement, the Guild and its locals heightened their opposition to race and gender discrimination in news industry hiring and promotion practices during the 1960s and 1970s.
The charismatic, energetic Broun, whose politics were forged in the Socialist Party, served as president of the New York Guild for its first six years. Early organizing campaigns enjoyed considerable success. In 1935, the New York Post became the first New York newspaper to unionize, followed by the Daily News in 1936, and the New York Times in 1941. The first magazine to unionize was Time in 1937.
The NGNY has carried out lengthy strikes against several major New York newspapers, including the 16-week Brooklyn Eagle strike of 1937, the 11-week World-Telegram and Sun strike of 1950, and the five-month Daily News strike of 1990-1991.
In 1995, the The Newspaper Guild merged with Communication Workers of America (CWA), and in 1997 it became a sector of the CWA. As of 2011, TNG-CWA represents 34,000 members. The Newspaper Guild of New York represents employees of major dailies, weeklies, many publications of the City's ethnic communities, magazines and other publications of non-profit organizations such as Consumers Union, and news and data services.
Scope and Content Note
The Newspaper Guild of New York Records includes administrative and general files of the NGNY (including material on its parent union, The Newspaper Guild), and extensive files on individual "shops" or branches, which are generally associated with a specific employer or publication. Shop files document bargaining, contract negotiations, grievances and arbitrations, social and political activities of shops, elections, the work of officers and staff, and changing technology, working conditions, and industry trends.
The collection is divided into Early Records (Series I-II), dating from the 1930s to 1950; and more recent records (Series III-V), dating from 1951 to the 1990s. Photographs contained in Series VII date from 1940-1950.
Arrangement
The files are organized into seven series:
Series I: Early Records: General Files, 1935-1950
Series II: Early Records: Shop Files, 1935-1950
Series III: General Files, 1951-1998
Series IV: Minutes, 1951-1991
Series V: Shop Files, 1951-1998
Series V:A: General Shop Files, 1951-1998
Series V:B: New York Daily News Shop Files
Series V:C: New York Times Shop Files
Series VI: Unprocessed Materials
Series VII: Photographs, 1940-1950
Folders are arranged alphabetically.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Newspaper Guild of New York Film Collection (FILM 009)
Newspaper Guild of New York: Betsy Wade Files (WAG 045)
Newspaper Guild Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 002)
Newsmen's Commission to Investigate the Murder of George Polk Records (TAM 159)
New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection (OH 001)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Given to Tamiment Library on deposit by the Newspaper Guild of New York in 1996. The accession numbers associated with these materials are 1986.019 and 1986.020. Additional materials were transferred in approximately 1998.
The accession numbers NPA.1999.016, NPA.2002.008, NPA.2002.011, NPA.2003.078 and NPA.2008.020 are also associated with this collection.
Custodial History
The archived website was migrated from the California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service to the Internet Archive's Archive-It Service in November 2015. The link to California Digital Library was removed in October 2017.
Press |x Employees |x Labor unions |z United States.; Publishers and publishing |z United States |x History.; New York (N.Y.); Newsletters.; Labor unions -- Elections -- United States.; Journalists -- Labor unions.; Fliers (printed matter); Correspondence.; New Jersey.; Minutes (administrative records); Labor unions |x Publishing |z United States.; Labor unions -- Officials and employees.; Contracts; Reports.; Time, inc..; Newsweek, inc.; Newspaper Guild.; New York World-Telegram.; New York Times Company.; New York Post.; New York Herald Tribune (Firm).; New York Amsterdam News.; Murphy, Thomas J., 1906-1998; Long Island Daily Press.; Lipton, Barry; Foreign Policy Association.; Journal American.; Egan, Edwin R.; El Diario (New York, NY).; Daily news (New York, N.Y.).; Deegan, John E.; Broun, Heywood, 1888-1939; Consumer Reports (Firm).; American Newspaper Guild.; Brooklyn Eagle.; Newspaper Guild of New York
- Series I: Early Records: General Files, 1935-1950
  Scope and Content Note
  Series I: Early Records: General Files, 1935-1950, documents the activities and operations of the NGNY and the ANG in their early years. The series includes correspondence, committee files, officers' files, election files, convention records, publications, and subject files.
  - Abbott and Adams, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ABC News Agency, 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ABC Newspapers in the US under Guild Contracts, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration: Guild Headquarters, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administration Program, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air Conditioning Newspaper Guild Club, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Arbitrations Association, 1944-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Committee for the Protection of the Foreign Born, 1943-1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Communication Association, 1939-1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Federal Labor: Trade Union Directory, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Hungarian Relief, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Institute of International Information, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Jewish Labor Council, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Labor Party, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American League for a Free Palestine, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Legion Post, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Newspaper Guild (ANG): Assessments, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ANG: Bridgeport, CT, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ANG: Brown Memorial Award, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ANG: Chain Paper Bulletin, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ANG: Clippings, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ANG: Collective Bargaining Advisory Committee, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ANG: Constitution Questions, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ANG: Contracts, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ANG: Contracts Committee, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ANG: Contracts Survey, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ANG Convention, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - ANG Convention, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ANG Convention, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ANG Convention, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ANG Convention (I), 1947 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - ANG Convention (II), 1947 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ANG Convention, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ANG Convention, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - ANG Convention, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ANG Convention: Address, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ANG Convention: Address and Radio Script, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - ANG Convention: Auditor's Report, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - ANG Convention: Ballots (Alternatives), 1944 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - ANG Convention: Ballots (Delegates), 1944 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - ANG Convention: By-Law Changes, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - ANG Convention: Clippings, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - ANG Convention: Committees and Delegates, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - ANG Convention: Committee Reports, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - ANG Convention: Constitution Commission, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ANG Convention: Correspondence, 1944; 1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ANG Convention: Credentials, 1947-1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ANG Convention: Delegates, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ANG Convention: Delegates, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ANG Convention: Delegates, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ANG Convention: Draft Program and Resolutions, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ANG Convention: Finances, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ANG Convention: General, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ANG Convention: IEB Report, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ANG Convention: Mail Ballots, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ANG Convention: McManus, John, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ANG Convention: Newspaper Commission, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ANG Convention: Officers Report, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 13a)
  - ANG Convention: Opposition Program, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ANG Convention: Program, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ANG Convention: Program, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ANG Convention: Program, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ANG Convention: Program, May 1945 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ANG Convention: Referendum, Apr 1945 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ANG Convention: Reports, Apr 1945 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - ANG Convention: Reports, Apr 1945 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ANG Convention: Reports and Addresses, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ANG Convention: Reports and Recommendations, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - ANG Convention: Representation, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - ANG Convention: Representative Assembly, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 24a)
  - ANG Convention: Travel and Hotel, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - ANG Convention: Travel and Hotel, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - ANG Convention: Travel and Hotel, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - ANG Convention: Travel and Hotel, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - ANG Convention: Travel and Hotel, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - ANG Convention: Wire Service Council Recommendations, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 29a)
  - ANG Convention: Women's Auxiliary, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - ANG: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - ANG: Correspondence, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - ANG: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ANG Elections, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 2a)
  - ANG Elections, 1941-1944 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - ANG Elections, 1947 (Box 553, Folder 1, 3)
  - ANG Elections, 1949 (Box 553, Folder 4)
  - ANG Elections: Convention, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2b)
  - ANG Elections: Convention, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates (I), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates (II), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates and Election Committee Rules, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Delegates and Election Committee Rules, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ANG Elections: Convention Left Wing Opposition, 1940-1950 (Box 3a, Folder 1)
  - ANG Elections: Executive Positions, 1949 (Box 3a, Folder 1a)
  - ANG Elections: Officers, 1947 (Box 3a, Folder 2)
  - ANG Elections: President Kenneth Crawford, 1939 (Box 3a, Folder 3)
  - ANG Elections: Regional Vice President, 1944 (Box 3a, Folder 4)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 5)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, Contributions, 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 6)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, Correspondence (I), 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 7)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, Correspondence (II), 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 8)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, Guild Reporter, 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 9)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, Literature, 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 10)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, Mail Ballots, 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 11)
  - ANG Elections: Secretary-Treasurer Charles Whipple, Pamphlet Material, 1945 (Box 3a, Folder 12)
  - ANG Elections: Vice President, 1943 (Box 3a, Folder 13)
  - ANG: Empire State District Council, 1943-1945 (Box 3b, Folder 1)
  - ANG: Empire State District Council, 1946 (Box 3b, Folder 2)
  - ANG: Empire State District Council, 1947-1949 (Box 3b, Folder 3)
  - ANG: Finance Committee Report, 1947 (Box 3b, Folder 4)
  - ANG: General, 1940 (Box 3b, Folder 4a)
  - ANG: General, 1945-1948 (Box 3b, Folder 5)
  - ANG: General, 1949 (Box 3b, Folder 6)
  - ANG: Guild Shop Questionnaire, 1940 (Box 3b, Folder 7)
  - ANG: Honorary Guild Membership, 1946 (Box 3b, Folder 8)
  - ANG: International Executive Board (IEB), 1939-1950 (Box 3b, Folder 9)
  - ANG: International Representatives, 1946; 1950 (Box 3b, Folder 10)
  - ANG: Leadership Training Conference, 1950 (Box 3b, Folder 11)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1943 (Box 3b, Folder 12)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1944 (Box 3b, Folder 13)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1945 (Box 3b, Folder 14)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1946 (Box 3b, Folder 15)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1947 (Box 3b, Folder 16)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1948 (Box 3b, Folder 17)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1949 (Box 3b, Folder 18)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, 1950 (Box 3b, Folder 19)
  - ANG: Membership in Good Standing, Analysis of 1946-1947 (Box 3b, Folder 20)
  - ANG: Midwest Conference, 1945 (Box 3b, Folder 21)
  - ANG: Midwest District Council, 1948 (Box 3b, Folder 22)
  - ANG: Minimum Wage Schedules in ANG Contracts, undated (Box 3b, Folder 23)
  - ANG: Model Contract, 1945-1950 (Box 3b, Folder 24)
  - ANG: National Collective Bargaining Advisory Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 3b, Folder 25)
  - ANG: Policy under Taft Hartley Act, 1948 (Box 3b, Folder 26)
  - ANG: National Wage Conference, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - ANG: "The Newsprint Problem", 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ANG: Organizer, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ANG: Organizing Reports, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - ANG: Pennsylvania District Council, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ANG: "Project X", Anti-Newspaper Monopoly, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ANG: Referendum: Dues Scale, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ANG: Referendum: Paid Presidency, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ANG: Texas District Council, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ANG: Wage Conference, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ANG: Wage Price Bulletin, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ANG: Wage Program, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ANG: Youngstown Resolution, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - American Newspaper Publishers Association, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - American Newspaper Writers Association, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - American Peace Mobilization, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - American Press Society, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - American Red Cross, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - American Red Cross: Servicemen's Tea, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Annual Ball, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Annual Benefit, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Anti-Guild Campaign (The Press House Inquiry), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Anti-Discrimination, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Anti-Semitism, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Applications for Jobs, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Arbitrations, 1945-1949 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Arbitrations Problems, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Arbitrators, 1941-1947 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Arkansas Guild Strike, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Armed Forces (Civil Rights), 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Association of Catholic Trade Unions, 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Association of Foreign Press Correspondents, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Associate Units, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Associate Units, 1940-1949 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Associate Units, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Athletics, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Australian Journalists Association, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Auxiliary, 1937-1942 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Auxiliary, 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Bad Standing List, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Bennett (James Gordon) Memorial, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Bentley, Gladys, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bid Top, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Billboard: Clippings, 1940s (Box 4, Folder 44a)
  - Bird and Bottle Party, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Board of Education (Inter-Religious and Inter-Racial Programs in Schools), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Boyle, Jerry, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Bretton Woods, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Breit, Harvey, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Bridges, Harry, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Broun, Heywood, 1934-1944 (Box 5, Folder 1a)
  - Browder, Earl, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Burkhardt, William, Jr., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - By-Laws (Changes), 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - By-Laws (Changes), 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - By-Laws (Changes), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Callahan, Major H. North, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Canteen, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Case Bill, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Casner, Mike (New York News Association), undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Catholic Institute of the Press, 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Trade Unionists, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cheeseborough Building Company, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Chicago Hearst Strike, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Chicago Hearst Strike: Film, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Chicago Hearst Strike: Finances, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chicago Hearst Strike: Play, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Chicago Sun, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - China Resolution, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cincinnati Referendum: Request for Mail Ballots, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - City-Wide Collective Bargaining Bulletin, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - City-Wide Conference, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - City-Wide Conference, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - City-Wide Conference (I), 1947 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - City-Wide Conference (II), 1947 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - City-Wide Collective Bargaining Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 27a)
  - City-Wide Contract, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - City-Wide Contract, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - City-Wide Council Meeting, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - City-Wide Elections, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - City-Wide Elections, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - City-Wide Elections: Local Officers, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 1a)
  - City-Wide Elections: Officers, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - City-Wide Elections: Officers, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - City-Wide Elections: Petitions, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3a)
  - City-Wide Elections: United Guild Campaign Literature, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3b)
  - City-Wide General, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3c)
  - City-Wide Minimums, 1940's (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - City-Wide Negotiations, 1942-1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - City-Wide Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - City-Wide Organizing Committee, 1947; 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5a)
  - City-Wide Six Units Meetings, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Civilian Defense, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights Congress, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland Press, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "Closed Shop" Strike, Duluth, 1937-1939; 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10a)
  - Club (Newspaper Guild Club), 1943-1950 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Club: Bar and Dining Room Income (I), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Club: Bar and Dining Room Income (II), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Club Membership, 1941-1946 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Club Rentals, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Club Rentals, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 15a)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Collective Bargaining: 1000 Hour Provision, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Collective Bargaining: Arbitrations, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Collective Bargaining: Arguments, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Collective Bargaining: Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Collective Bargaining: Conference, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Collective Bargaining: Conference, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Collective Bargaining: Conference, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Collective Bargaining: Consumer Credit, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Collective Bargaining: Cost of Living, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Collective Bargaining: Death Benefits, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Collective Bargaining: Fair labor Standards Act, 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Collective Bargaining: Guild Plan, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 29)